slicehost.com 2012-10-28

# Slicehost Privacy Policy // Slicehost VPS Hosting is now Rackspace Cloud Servers hosting

### Slicehost Privacy Policy

Slicehost LLC has created a privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to data privacy and protection. This policy sets forth our information gathering and utilization practices for the www.slicehost.com, manage.slicehost.com, and api.slicehost.com websites.

#### What We Collect and Where

Our websites use several different forms that can be used to request information about or procurement of products, and services. From these forms, we collect the following information:

  * Customer’s contact information
  * Unique identifiers
  * Financial information
  * Live Chat Messages

Slicehost does not intentionally gather personal data about visitors who are under the age of 13.

Slicehost does not view the files that you upload, download or store using our service, and does not monitor or disclose any information regarding your specific files and data without your permission, unless required by law applicable to Slicehost, or in accordance with this policy and our terms of service.

While Slicehost does not monitor, view or disclose the specific data stored using its service, it is necessary to track various aspects of your account to support features including, but not limited to, bandwidth monitoring, cpu and storage usage. In the course of technical troubleshooting, we may on occasion be required to mount and inspect your file system, monitor traffic to and from your slice and monitor CPU usage.

####  How Secure is the Information We Collect? 

Slicehost is committed to industry best practices approaches concerning security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information in our possession. Credit Card information is encrypted during transmission, and our company databases are accessible only by persons who have entered into and are bound by a confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement with Slicehost.

To protect your account information and data, please keep your passwords and Application Programming Interface (API) key private. 

#### Contact Information 

We use customer information to send via email pertinent administrative communications regarding their accounts or our services. This information will not be used in a manner different than the purpose for which it was originally collected, unless Slicehost has first obtained your consent to do so.

A Customer may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information they have submitted to Slicehost by updating their account on our website. If you cancel your account, your personal data and other information may be retained in our archive or backup records; however, credit card numbers are not retained.

####  Financial Information

We may ask visitors to enter credit card or account information through manage.slicehost.com. Credit card information is encrypted for its protection prior to its transmission over the internet. We collect this information on a transaction-by-transaction basis. We will not authorize the release of the information with anyone not directly involved in processing the transaction. This information may be encrypted and stored for logging purposes in accordance with applicable regulatory requirements. 

#### Cookies

We use cookies to collect non-personal data that enables us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our service. Cookies are unique text files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. Disabling the use of cookies may affect your ability to use some features of our service.

Slicehost also collects general information about visits to our websites. This information includes parameters such as the number of visits and browser details. No personal details are present in this data and it is utilized for the sole purpose of better understanding website usage to improve user experiences

#### Links to Third Party Sites

The Slicehost websites may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy, and you should review those policies prior to using the websites. Slicehost has no responsibility for linked websites and these links are provided solely for the convenience and information of users.

All information collected by Slicehost is used for purposes of facilitating our services, providing support to users, improving our services, and administration. We will not sell or market the email addresses or other collected personal information of our customers to any third parties not affiliated with us.

#### Contacting Slicehost

If you have questions about this policy please contact Slicehost using one of the following options:

Email:

privacy@slicehost.com

Mail:

Attn: Privacy Policy  
Slicehost LLC  
112 Pecan Street  
San Antonio, Texas 78205

#### Revisions To The Privacy Statement

Slicehost reserves the right in its sole discretion to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification of this policy will be posted on the Slicehost websites, and a user’s continued use of the service and the websites will signify agreement to such changes.
